Viewers, thank you.
Those under dominion, those under bondage of sickness, disease -
receive freedom, in the name of Jesus!
To be greedy as well - "receive, receive" - is bondage.
It is bondage because when you believe in "receive, receive", you can never grow.
You must be a cheerful person - a cheerful giver, first to God.
First to God is sacrifice - what you cherish, what you love most, what your life depends on.
You look at your wardrobe - you are giving what you have not been using.
You give it to friends - you can give it sometimes but many times (give) what your life depends on,
what you cherish most.
You have to balance your life - what you do not need, what you need.
If you give sometimes what you do not need, come back again - what you need.
What you do not need, what you need.
Not all the time what you do not need.
If God was giving you what you do not need, how would your life look like?
Whatever you do to the least out there, that you do to God.
Like I have said: They need you more than we need you here.
In terms of finances, support, your neighbour needs you more than we need you here.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Those under bondage, those under dominion of sickness, disease -
receive freedom, in the name of Jesus!
I command deliverance on you right now, in the name of Jesus!
I command deliverance on you now, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see the downfall of satan.
I command deliverance on you now, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command healing on you now, in the name of Jesus!
Jesus heals every disease, every infirmity, every wound - be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
This is freedom!
Freedom!
Right now, begin to fix your life.
Begin to fix your life by the authority of Jesus.
Fix your life!
Fix your marriage!
Fix your career!
Fix your family!
Fix your health!
Begin to fix your health!
I can see your life being fixed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The authority that pulled down the walls of Jericho,
right now, begin to pull down, tear down, destroy every demonic stronghold in your life,
every demonic stronghold between you and God's promises -
right now, begin to tear it down!
Pull it down!
Right now, open your lips.
The SCOAN Altar
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I have seen the downfall of satan!
In your life, I have seen.
Confess it.
I have seen the downfall of satan!
I have seen the downfall of satan in my business!
I have seen the downfall of satan in my life!
I have seen the downfall of satan in my marriage!
I have seen the downfall of satan in my career!
I have seen the downfall of satan, in Jesus Christ's name!
Let the people of God say, "Amen!"
Merry Christmas!
Happy New Year!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Mel Flowers 04/01/2019
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 05/01/2019